Jacob Lee

Contact

Address

Upper Caboolture, QLD., 4510

Phone

042-379-7821

E-mail

Jacob.lee80@outlook.com

Skills

Excellent Communication and interpersonal skills

Ability to work as a team member and or autonomously

Strong organizational skills

Strong delivery of customer service and customer focus

Ability to use discretion and initiative.

High level of self-motivation, integrity, honesty, impartiality and transparency.

Microsoft office, computer skills

Emailing

Report writing

File and records management

Since December 2006 I was employed by the Queensland Police Service (QPS). I was a general duties police officer for 10+ years before retiring from the police in 2020. Policing has provided me with some unique and challenging experiences. It has provided me with excellent communication and conflict resolution skills, office administration duties with data entry. I have been in management positions for most of my earlier career. This also included office administration duties, liaising with sales reps and invoicing, cash handling, banking duties, stock ordering etc.

I can work either autonomously or as part of a team and I have no problems or concerns in continuous study or completing accredited courses required for the position.

I am passionate in working in a team and supporting relevant stakeholders.

Work History

2007-07 *-*2020-10

Constable

Queensland Police Service, Brisbane, Old

- · Undertake operational patrols
- Perform administrative duties, prepare forms, correspondence and reports
- Gather and exchange information
- Monitored and mentored first year officers who have recently graduated from cadet training
- · Provide the public with service and support
- · Investigate incidents or offences
- Knowledge of legislative and compliance relevant to QPS.
- Managed crime scenes to protect personnel and preserve evidence.
- · Made forcible arrests when necessary.
- · Data Entry
- · Adherence to criminal code act 1899
- · Weapons Licensing
- Public safety Preservations act 1986
- · Work health and safety procedures
- · Communication and conflict

2007-03 -2007-07

Duty Manager

Finnegan's Chin, Kallangur, Old

- · Handling customer and employee issues
- Overseeing operations, including maintenance, cleanliness and efficiency
- · Ensuring that security and safety regulations are met
- Address customer/employee issues and complaints.
- · Trained employees in essential job functions.
- Handled employee-related issues to improve performance, professional conduct and attendance reliability.
- Opened and closed location and monitored shift changes to uphold successful operations strategies and maximize business success.
- Set goals for department and supported employees in meeting expectations.

2005-01 -2006-01

Assistant Manager/Lifeguard

Burpengary Aquatic Centre, Burpengary, QLD

- · Ensuring safety of customers
- Performing CPR (if required)
- · Perform pool rescue (if required)
- · Maintenance and cleaning of pools
- Janitor cleaning duties (winter only)
- · Day to day running of the business
- · Preparing employee rosters.

2001-01 -2004-01

Duty Manager/Gaming/Bar/Security

Caboolture Sports Club, Caboolture, Old

- Responded to customer concerns by providing friendly, knowledgeable support and maintaining composure and professionalism.
- Initiated plans to improve customer relations, quality standards and service efficiency.
- Handled employee-related issues to improve performance, professional conduct and attendance reliability.
- · Trained employees in essential job functions.

Education

Senior Certificate

Caboolture High School

Diploma of Hospitality Management

Caboolture TAFE

Diploma of Policing